Today is a bummer.
Rock Bottom is a comedy film directed by Dylan Meyer.
Rock Bottom chronicles the cosmic/comic misadventures of a girl undergoing a life crisis after she locks herself out of her
apartment with no pants on and is thereby forced to confront her emotional, philosophical, and logistical problems.
Dwayne Douglas Johnson (born May 2, 1972), also known by his ring name
"the Rock", is an American actor and professional wrestler.
He is signed to WWE, where he performs on a part-time basis.
Widely regarded as one of the greatest professional wrestlers of all time, Johnson was integral to the
development and success of the World Wrestling Federation (WWF, now WWE) during the Attitude Era.
He wrestled for the WWF full-time for eight years
before pursuing an acting career.
His films have grossed over $11.4 billion worldwide, making him one
of the world's highest-grossing actors of all time.
He is a co-owner of the United Football League, a member of the board of directors of TKO Group
Holdings—the parent company of UFC and WWE—and co-founder of Seven Bucks Productions.
After accepting an athletic scholarship to play football at the University of Miami, Johnson was
a member of the 1991 national championship team but was largely a backup player.
Despite aspirations to play professional football, he went undrafted in the 1995 NFL draft, and
briefly signed with the Calgary Stampeders before being cut in his first season.
In 1996, his father assisted in helping him secure a contract with the WWF.
Johnson quickly rose to global prominence, aided by a gimmick
he employed as a charismatic trash talker.
Johnson left the WWE in 2004; he returned in 2011 as a part-time performer until 2013 and made sporadic
appearances until his retirement in 2019; in 2023, he returned once again on a part-time basis.
A 10-time world champion—including the promotion's first of African-American descent—he is also a two-time Intercontinental
Champion, a five-time Tag Team Champion, the 2000 Royal Rumble winner, and WWE's sixth Triple Crown champion.
Johnson headlined multiple pay-per-view events, including WWE's flagship event WrestleMania six times (15, 16, 17, 28, 29, and 40 – Night 1) which includes the most-bought
professional wrestling pay-per-view (WrestleMania 28) and main evented the most-watched episodes of WWE's flagship television series (Raw and SmackDown).
Johnson's first film role was in The Mummy Returns (2001).
The next year, he played his first leading role in the
action fantasy film The Scorpion King.
He has since starred in family films The Game Plan (2007), Race to Witch Mountain (2009), Tooth Fairy (2010), Jumanji: Welcome to the Jungle
(2017), Jumanji: The Next Level (2019), and Jungle Cruise (2021), and the action films Journey 2: The Mysterious Island (2012), G.I.
Joe: Retaliation (2013), Hercules (2014), Skyscraper
(2018), San Andreas (2015) and Rampage (2018).
He also starred in the action comedy films Get Smart (2008), Central
Intelligence (2016), Baywatch (2017), and Red Notice (2021).
His role as Luke Hobbs in the Fast & Furious films, beginning with Fast Five
(2011), helped the franchise become one of the highest-grossing in film.
He joined the DC Extended Universe by playing the
title role in Black Adam (2022).
He has also voiced Maui in the Disney animated film Moana (2016), and its sequel Moana
2 (2024), and will reprise the role in the 2026 live-action remake.
He received critical praise for his dramatic turn as MMA fighter Mark
Kerr in the sports biopic The Smashing Machine (2025).
Johnson produced and starred in the HBO comedy-drama series Ballers
(2015–2019) and the autobiographical sitcom Young Rock (2021–2023).
His autobiography, The Rock Says, was released in 2000
and was a New York Times bestseller.
In 2016 and 2019, Time named him as one of the world's most influential people.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.